nintendo-scene.com 2009-06-19

# Privacy Policy | Nintendo-Scene

**Privacy Policy**

**�� Privacy Policy**

Latest Update: 23 February 2007  
Nintendo-scene is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect personal information you provide online.

**�� What this Privacy Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy covers Nintendo-scene’s treatment of personally identifiable information that Nintendo-scene collects when you are on the Nintendo-scene site, and when you use Nintendo-scene services. This policy also covers Nintendo-scene’s treatment of any personally identifiable information that Nintendo-scene’s partners share with Nintendo-scene.  
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Nintendo-scene does not own or control or to people that Nintendo-scene does not employ or manage.

**�� Information Collection and Use**

Nintendo-scene collects personally identifiable information when you register for a Nintendo-scene account and when you use certain Nintendo-scene services. Nintendo-scene may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.  
When you register with Nintendo-scene, we ask for several details which may or may not include your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Even though you register with Nintendo-scene and sign in to our services, you are still anonymous to us.  
Nintendo-scene also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Nintendo-scene cookie information and the page you requested. This information is used only for internal purposes by Nintendo-scene technical support staff.  
Nintendo-scene uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services.

**�� Information Sharing and Disclosure**

It is policy that personal information, such as your name, postal and e-mail address or telephone number, is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you may provide us, such as through our forum, chat or by email used only for the purposes for which you provide the information. For example, if you choose to give your name and/or any other personal information it is completely by your own will.  
Nintendo-scene will not solicit or provide any private information to outside vendors or organizations. Information you choose to submit on our site is for public view and at your discretion. Therefore any information you submit publicly on Nintendo-scene by way of forums or chats can be viewed by outside sources. Any emails submitted to any member of Nintendo-scene will remain privately held and no such information will be made public unless user permission is granted.  
Nintendo-scene will ONLY send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:

We have your consent to share the information;  
We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process.

**�� Cookies**

Nintendo-scene may set and access Nintendo-scene cookies on your computer.  
Nintendo-scene allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Nintendo-scene’s cookies.

**�� Third Party Advertising**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**�� Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

Nintendo-scene gives you the ability to edit your Nintendo-scene Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want Nintendo-scene to contact you.  
You may request deletion of your Nintendo-scene account by contacting us here with your account details

**�� Security**

Your Nintendo-scene Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.

**�� Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Nintendo-scene may amend this policy from time to time without prior warning. Please check [http://www.Nintendo-scene.com/privacy-policy](http://www.nintendo-scene.com/privacy-policy) for the latest version.

**Nintendo-scene is not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of any affiliates or 3rd party organizations displayed within our website.**

If you have questions or suggestions you can contact us at  

[feedback[at]Nintendo-scene.com](mailto:feedback@Nintendo-scene.com)
